So we've ridden the roller coaster up one hill, down a trough, up another hill and now for round four we're going back in to the valley.
And what that means is we have to make our best four card low hand.
Now we already know from a previous round that I don’t have any low action going on so I’m not going to play this hand.
Okay, and we know from a previous round that this guy doesn't have any low action going on.
He's not going to play this hand.
But you and this fellow say "one, two, three" and show your chip and show each other your hands.
And this is your hand; you've got what's called a "queen low".
You've got queen-seven-three-ace.
At this point, if this guy doesn't have and ace but has something lower than a queen and nothing higher than a queen he's got you.
Alas, he got a pair of sevens there, so no working four card low and you take the pot and he pays.
Not even sure why he stayed in the hand except for the sake of our experiment.
You win the pot of sixteen and he matches the pot of sixteen and we're on to round five.